Preiminary guide to the Rich Gold papers M1510
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Rich Gold papers
circa 1978-2005
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Gold, Rich (Richard Goldstein)
LaPalma, Marina
M1510
20 Linear Feet
Collection includes: notebooks (114), manuscripts, documentation, artwork, correspondence, and the manuscript for his currently unpublished book, The Plenitude. Also included are boxes of patents, awards, slides, video tapes, audio tapes, CDs, photographs, and documentation materials (including the World Economic Forums of 1999, 2000, and 2001).
Box 1
Folder 1
Scope and Content
Collection includes: notebooks (114), manuscripts, documentation, artwork, correspondence, and the manuscript for his currently unpublished book, The Plenitude. Also included are boxes of patents, awards, slides, video tapes, audio tapes, CDs, photographs, and documentation materials (including the World Economic Forums of 1999, 2000, and 2001).
Biographical Note
Rich Gold was a digital artist, inventor, cartoonist, composer, lecturer and inter-disciplinary researcher. He was a provocative speaker who lectured throughout the world on the future of the book, the nature of engineering, creativity, innovation and Evocative Knowledge Objects (EKOs) [from the Rich Gold website, 5/13/2011]
Acquisition Note
Purchased, 2005. Accession 2005-343
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research; material must be requested at least 36 hours in advance of intended use
Science -- History -- Gaming; Gold, Rich (Richard Goldstein); LaPalma, Marina
- Series 1: Miscellaneous
  - Death Announcement (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Dear Mom and Dad (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - 2 Clever by Half (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Sketchup (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Travel to Sheldon (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Toy (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Condolence (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - CU (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Dell (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Gateway (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Buffalo, NY (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Degree, Mills1978 May 21 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Seattle (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Minneapolis (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Baltimore (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Travel (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Travel to Ottowa (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Lingo (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - CV (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Address Lists (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Onomy Labs, Inc. (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - De Reis van de Ingenieur by Ton Meijknecht and Hans van Drongelen (Box 21)
  - Polaris Road (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Herbert Goldstein (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Business Cards [1 of 4] (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Business Cards [2 of 4] (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Business Cards [3 of 4] (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Business Cards [4 of 4] (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Coast Guard "Thank You" Plaque - Innovation and Technology Workshop9/1/1988 (Box 83)
  - Wedding gift from Jim Pomeroy12/1/1979 (Box 83, Folder 6)
- Series 2: Photos
  - AIR Photos (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - EAT Reunion (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Web Picture B&W (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Old Photos (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Xerox (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - TAB RITE Aart, Oakland1979 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Paper Copies (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Performances, Travel, Dad (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - PARC, 1990's (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Series 3: Other Artists/Exhibitions
  - IXNA (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Electronic Literature Organization (Box 3)
  - Christoph Zellweger (Box 3)
  - Interaction Design Institute IVREA (Box 3)
  - Walker Art Center 1998-1999 Annual Report "Through Your Eyes" (Box 3)
  - Performative Science (Box 3)
  - Dropped Lines (Box 3)
  - Marina La Palma [1 of 2] (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Marina La Palma [2 of 2] (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Abstracting Craft (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Tacit Dimension (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Bodies Incorporated (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - the LAB (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Big Things from Little Computers (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Offprint Excerpt (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Clusters of Creativity (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Federation Square (Box 21)
  - ZMK "Hardware Software Artware" (Box 21)
  - Clusters of Creativity Galley Proof2002 July 01 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Stanley the Seal of Approval by Stan Resnicoff (Box 36)
  - Hélio Oitica (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Jack Vees Guitar Toss1993 November 04 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Billy's Good Advice (Box 83, Folder 4)
- Series 4: Proposals
  - XFR Summative Evaluation for the Tech Museum of Innovation2000 April (Box 4)
  - Technology@Play (2 copies)2001 April 02 (Box 4)
  - Billboard Love1988 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Proposal for a book1980 April 18 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - The Tech (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Walker1990 February 20 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - PACT: Xerox and Goldstar1994 November 15 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Patents (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - MIRI Walk in Book (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - HAVOC (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Briefing Materials Butterfly Discovery Park Draft Strategy Charrette1997 July (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Neoteny (Box 52, Folder 3)
- Series 5: Slides
  - 35 Sheets of Slides (Box 5)
- Series 6: Manuals
  - Agentsheets: A Tool for Building Domain-Oriented Dynamic, Visual Environments1993 December (Box 6)
  - VRML Examples (Box 6)
  - The Annotated VRML Reference Manual (Box 6)
  - The Virtual Reality Modeling Language International Standard1997 (Box 6)
  - VRML2001 (Box 6)
  - Havok Xtra Lingo Reference Guide2000 (Box 6)
  - Sun Labs - The First Five Years: The First 50 Technical Reports1998 September (Box 6)
  - Sun Microsystems Laboratories The First 10 Years 1991-20012001 October (Box 6)
  - Red Creek (Box 21)
  - Three-Dimensional Virtual Acoustic Displays (Box 21)
  - MITRE (Box 21, Folder 2)
- Series 7: Magazines
  - Computer vol 34 no 12001 January (Box 7)
  - Commodore vol 4 no 51985 December (Box 7)
  - Invisible City nos 26-271980 August (Box 7)
  - Invisible City no 281981 December (Box 7)
  - Vanity Fair no 4892001 May (Box 7)
  - Axis vol 912001 May (Box 7)
  - Communications vol 35 no 51992 May (Box 7)
  - Scientific American vol 257 no 31987 September (Box 7)
  - Leonardo Music Journal vol 81998 (Box 7)
  - Leonardo vol 35 no 22002 (Box 7)
  - Leonardo vol 34 no 32001 (Box 7)
  - The Byte Book of Computer Music1979 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - American Art, vol 7 no 41993 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Clippings (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - New Music Alliance (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Leonardo Book Series2002 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Scientific American (copy) 1991 September (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - American Art Final1993 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Scientific American, vol 257 no 31987 September (Box 21)
  - Intreactions vol 8 no 32001 (Box 21)
  - Siggraph 2001Electronic Art and Animation Catalog (Box 52, Folder 17)
- Series 8: Games
  - Internet (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Scheme (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Early Notebooks1983 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - John Kao (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Gameboy Zine (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Game Sprite (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Little Computer People (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Malcolm Kaufman (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Project Alpha Partnership (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - 3D Squash (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Graffitti Face (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - MATSPK1987 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Ronald Regan Conversational Satire (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Little Computer People Activision envelope and Proof1985 (Box 52, Folder 13)
  - M.E.N.C.H. (Box 52, Folder 14)
  - Mattel Toys Chairman's Awards1989 (Box 83, Folder 1)
- Series 9: Notebooks
  - 14 Notebooks (Box 9)
  - 14 Notebooks (Box 10)
  - 14 Notebooks (Box 11)
  - 8 Notebooks (Box 12)
  - 7 Notebooks (Box 13)
  - 8 Notebooks (Box 14)
  - 13 Notebooks (Box 15)
  - 10 Notebooks (Box 16)
  - 8 Notebooks (Box 17)
  - 10 Notebooks (Box 18)
  - 22 Notebooks (Box 19)
  - Bust in Plastic (Box 19)
  - 14 Notebooks (Box 20)
  - Strathmore Sketch Pad (Box 23)
- Series 10: Festivals/Conferences
  - Vanguard Reconnaissance The Implications of Universal Publishing1986 November (Box 6)
  - Technische Universiteit Eindhoven IPO Annual Progress Report no. 352000 (Box 21)
  - Technische Universiteit Eindhoven IPO Annual Progress Report no. 341999 (Box 21)
  - Banff New Music Institute2002 (Box 21)
  - Engineering is Magic2002 November (Box 21)
  - Vanguard Forum1996 November (Box 22)
  - New Music America1980 June (Box 22)
  - ISEA 97 Eighth International Symposium on Electronic Art1997 September (Box 22)
  - SIGGRAPH 2001 (Box 22)
  - Foldback (Box 22)
  - Canadian Film Centre (Box 22)
  - RIT (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - ISEA 96 Paper1996 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Multimedia SF1994 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Dialectics of PAIR (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Printing in Future (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - PAIR Overheads (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - CDI Update Slides1996 June (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Toronto/Holland (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - San Francisco Art Institute The Annual1977 (Box 23)
  - University of Minnesota Management Information Systems Research Center Seminar Series (Box 23)
  - ICCH15 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - ZKM Institute of Visual media (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Karlsruhe (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - ARS Electronica (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Delft (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Digital Expression - The Media Laboratory1994 October 20 (Box 24)
  - Keynote Speakers, Inc.2002 (Box 24)
  - Fourth International Symposium on Electronic Art1993 November (Box 24)
  - Papers Fourth International Symposium on Electronic Art1993 November (Box 24)
  - Technologies for the 21st Century Roundtable in Multimedia1994 (Box 24)
  - American Anthropological Association 94th Annual Meeting1995 November (Box 24)
  - Proceedings of the Second International Conference on Auditory Display, ICAD '941994 November (Box 24)
  - New Music America Festival1984 July (Box 24)
  - New Music America Festival1981 (Box 24)
  - New Paradigms in Using Computers - Extreme User Interfaces2002 July (Box 24)
  - Experiments in the Future of Reading 2000 (Box 24)
  - Adelaide Festival (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Korea 1994 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - The Design Institute 1998-2000 (Box 47)
  - Australian Network for Art and Technology (Box 47)
  - ANAT Art and Science Residenct Program 1999-2001 (Box 47)
  - Design Camp University of Minnesota (Box 47)
  - 5th International Symposium on Electronic Art1994 August (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Interactive Design Institute (IVREA) postgraduate materials (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Minneapolis College of Art and Design 4th International Symposium on Electronic Art (Box 52, Folder 18)
  - Bridging the Gap? Science Art Humanity12/1/1979 (Box 83, Folder 7)
- Series 11: Artwork
  - An Introduction to the Serge Modular Music System1981 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Georgio (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Trouble at the Border (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Posters and Flyers (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - The Plentitude a Talk2002 (Box 25)
  - The Plentitude version .91993-2002 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Junk Tribe Book1995 February 23 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Junk Tribe1995 March 10 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Desktop Conquistador1991 January (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Cybernetic Oracle1976 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - How Smart Does Your Bed Have to Be, Before You Are Afraid to Go to Sleep at Night?1994 June 21 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - When My Father Mows the Lawn, Is He a Cyborg?1995 October (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Cyborgs1995 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - What Coin-Op (and other jobs) Taught Me1995 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Available Works (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Playing Cards (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Flat Comb Motel (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Multiples (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - The Year is 2501 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Career Stuff (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - I Primi Lavori di Rich Gold1979 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - VR Disc (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Available Works (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Performances 1970s (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Late PP Mail (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Sprauge (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Lost in Space (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Hyper-Henry (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Re: Harry the Ape1980 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - My Art (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - APRC '81 Stuff1981 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Rich Gold - '781978 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Hand - 8051 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Handwriting Routine1991 August 13 (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Flats (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Fractal Print-Outs from Able Was I (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Fractal Print-Outs from Able Was I (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - Able Was I (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - Booklets (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Goldographs and Sheets (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - General Goldograph Materials (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - NMA '811981 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Original Fictional Cultures1977 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Fictional Cultures Very Original1977 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Fictional Cultures Master1977 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Goldograph Serious Problems - Automatic Solutions1981 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - The Goldographs (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Goldograph Explanation Sheets (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - B Goldograph (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - B Goldograph Forward1974 August 26 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Original Goldo #11980 November (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Goldo #1 Stuff (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Original Goldo #2 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Goldo #2 Stuff (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Original Goldo #31981 March (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Goldo #3 Extra Stuff (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Goldograph #4 (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Goldo #5 Master (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - Goldo #61990 (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - Goldo #6 Covers (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - 10 Objects Undergoing Intensive Recombinatory Research at Goldographic Laboratories All Over the World1993 (Box 28, Folder 21)
  - Goldograph Stamp (Box 28, Folder 22)
  - Varied Artwork (Box 28, Folder 23)
  - Object Sketch (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Ned Sarti (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Collages and Collage Materials (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Paintings 10x10 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Fact Sheet 5 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - diary (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Cartoons 2/881988 February (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - 18 Drawings (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Sound Comb #2 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Pastels (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Re-do Cartoons (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Building Components1982 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Lecture, History of Acoustic Holes and Courses in Modern Golf (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Modern Golf (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Golf (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - American Art Copies (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Poetics of Ubi-Comp (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Ubiquitous Computing and the Future of the Contemporary Art Museum1996 (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - 10 Proverbs on Ubi-Art and the Art Museum2001 (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - Original Art in Age of Ubi-Comp Drawings (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - Art in Age of Ubi-Comp Transparency1993 (Box 29, Folder 21)
  - Rich Gold Has the Heebie Jeebies (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - Dealer See Also Nepenthe (Box 29, Folder 23)
  - Artificial Personalities1991 June 20 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - The Village of Idiots (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Apple Hill Center for Chamber Music (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Live Hearts #2 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Music from Fictional Cultures and Cybernetic Oracle (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Towards a Synthesis of the New Music Dialectic (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - The Vibrating Circular String in Outer Space (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Three Songs from a Vibrating Circular String Located in Outer Space1974 March (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Parking Cars or Pumping1974 January (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Model Home1982 November 06 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - 946131974 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Piece for Piano in Newhall1973 August (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Scores, Articles, Ideas, Poems, etc (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Break Glass in Case of Fire1978 (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Original Leauge Flyer1978 (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - Mills Tribute2005 Mat 05 (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - Should There Be Music? (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - Various (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - Rich Gold1974 January (Box 30, Folder 19)
  - Music Module1977 January (Box 30, Folder 20)
  - Colophon Club2000 April 11 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - The Thoughts of Virgule Period (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Creatures Tutorial (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - JPGR (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Syntactical Investigations1974 August (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Georgio Defined and Georgio In Paradise (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Georgio Poems (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Georgio at War flyer (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Georgio of the Suburbs1979 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Flyers (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Georgio at War Table of Contents (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Cartoon Sketches (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Drawings for Billboard Love (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Watch Out for Bricks! and Billboard Love1988 (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Watch Out for Bricks! 1988 (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - Pet Person1984 August (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - Train Game (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - Where's Waldo1990 November (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - CGI (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - Hearts Uncorrected Copy (Box 31, Folder 20)
  - Original Hearts (Box 31, Folder 21)
  - Monument to the Maimed Babies of the Korean War Personal Copy #11974 (Box 32)
  - Monument to the Maimed Babies of the Korean War First Draft (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Monument to the Maimed Babies of the Korean War Second Draft1974 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Monument to the Maimed Babies of the Korean War (typed copy)1974 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Griffon's Argot Draft (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Griffon's Argot (copy)1975 January (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Very Early Griffon's Argot 1974 December (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Misc (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Griffon's Argot1974 December (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Griffon's Argot (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Griffon's Argot (original) (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Cybernetic Oracle (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Rich Gold's Griffon's Argot [1 of 2]1975 January (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Rich Gold's Griffon's Argot [2 of 2]1975 January (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - A Text Booklet (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Goldograph #1 The Seasons1980 Nov (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Goldograph #2 Serious Problems - Automatic Solutions1981 Jan (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - Goldograph #3 Infidelity1981 Mar (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - Goldograph #5 Mummies1990 Oct (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - The Plentitude c2001 [1 of 2]2001 (Box 52, Folder 10)
  - The Plentitude c2001 [2 of 2]2001 (Box 52, Folder 11)
  - The Griffon's Argot1975 May (Box 52, Folder 12)
  - Miscellaneous Artwork and Flyers (Box 52, Folder 15)
  - Mad Politics and Bitter Mathematics or My Life as a Systems Anarchist1974 (Box 52, Folder 16)
  - An Illustrated and Exponential Autobiography and History of the World in Twelve Hours (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Photocopies: "I love you" and "Lonely Crowds" "Men" (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Tab Rite (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Red 'block heads' (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Blue-Card Paintings (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Tab Rite tabs un-numbered1979 Oct 27 (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - Other (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - Red Cards (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - (red) assortment glob grid spiral (Box 55, Folder 9)
  - red golf-heads intersetions (Box 55, Folder 10)
  - red 'relational' figures (Box 55, Folder 11)
  - Ponies Red (Box 55, Folder 12)
  - Red 'hexagons' (Box 55, Folder 13)
  - 10 x 10 Matrix wall piece of 10 Objects (and hybrids) with captions (Ten Objects Undergoing Intensive Recombinatory Research at Goldographic Laboratories All Over the World - Photocopies) (Box 55, Folder 14)
  - Blue Cards (Box 55, Folder 15)
  - Blue Card Paintings Originals1976-1978 (Box 55, Folder 16)
  - Small Card Studies1976-1978 (Box 55, Folder 17)
  - 10 Objects Studies clowns (Box 55, Folder 18)
  - Geometric Composition "drawings-under-tape" series1983 (Box 55, Folder 19)
  - 10 Objects Studies water color (Box 55, Folder 20)
  - Clown Furniture (Box 55, Folder 21)
  - 10 Objects Studies (Box 55, Folder 22)
  - Turtle Life (Box 55, Folder 23)
  - Small Wonder #6 (Box 55, Folder 24)
  - Lego Rendering NY Times Photo by Henry Goldstein age 112002 (Box 55, Folder 25)
  - [?] (Othertype 56)
  - A Periodic Cartoon Wall Diary [1 of 23]Jan Feb 1976 (Othertype 57)
  - A Periodic Cartoon Wall Diary [2 of 23]Jan Feb 1976 (Othertype 58)
  - A Periodic Cartoon Wall Diary [3 of 23]Jan Feb 1976 (Othertype 59)
  - A Periodic Cartoon Wall Diary [4 of 23]Jan Feb 1976 (Othertype 60)
  - A Periodic Cartoon Wall Diary [5 of 23]Jan Feb 1976 (Othertype 61)
  - A Periodic Cartoon Wall Diary [6 of 23]Jan Feb 1976 (Othertype 62)
  - A Periodic Cartoon Wall Diary [7 of 23]Jan Feb 1976 (Othertype 63)
  - A Periodic Cartoon Wall Diary [8 of 23]Jan Feb 1976 (Othertype 64)
  - A Periodic Cartoon Wall Diary [9 of 23]Jan Feb 1976 (Othertype 65)
  - A Periodic Cartoon Wall Diary [10 of 23]Jan Feb 1976 (Othertype 66)
  - A Periodic Cartoon Wall Diary [11 of 23]Jan Feb 1976 (Othertype 67)
  - A Periodic Cartoon Wall Diary [12 of 23]Jan Feb 1976 (Othertype 68)
  - A Periodic Cartoon Wall Diary [13 of 23]Jan Feb 1976 (Othertype 69)
  - A Periodic Cartoon Wall Diary [14 of 23]Jan Feb 1976 (Othertype 70)
  - A Periodic Cartoon Wall Diary [15 of 23]Jan Feb 1976 (Othertype 71)
  - A Periodic Cartoon Wall Diary [16 of 23]Jan Feb 1976 (Othertype 72)
  - A Periodic Cartoon Wall Diary [17 of 23]Jan Feb 1976 (Othertype 73)
  - A Periodic Cartoon Wall Diary [18 of 23]Jan Feb 1976 (Othertype 74)
  - A Periodic Cartoon Wall Diary [19 of 23]Jan Feb 1976 (Othertype 75)
  - A Periodic Cartoon Wall Diary [20 of 23]Jan Feb 1976 (Othertype 76)
  - A Periodic Cartoon Wall Diary [21 of 23]Jan Feb 1976 (Othertype 77)
  - A Periodic Cartoon Wall Diary [22 of 23]Jan Feb 1976 (Othertype 78)
  - A Periodic Cartoon Wall Diary [23 of 23]Jan Feb 1976 (Othertype 79)
  - Grids (Othertype 80)
  - Poster and "Able Was I" (Othertype 81)
  - 2 by 4 (Box 82, Folder 1)
  - Electronic Projects for Musicians (Box 82, Folder 2)
  - Glockenschlag (Box 82, Folder 3)
  - Brian Woodbury (Box 82, Folder 4)
  - Music Mouth (Box 82, Folder 5)
  - Charlie Morrow (Box 82, Folder 6)
  - Paul McMahon (Box 82, Folder 7)
  - Red Spot (Box 82, Folder 8)
  - She's -A-Wild (Box 82, Folder 9)
  - Afterimage (Box 82, Folder 10)
  - Primitive Romance (Box 82, Folder 11)
  - The Single Coils (Box 82, Folder 12)
  - Lovely Little Records featuring John Bischoff, Frankie Mann, Paul DeMarinis, "Blue" Gene Tyranny, Maggi Payne, and Phil Harmonic (Box 82, Folder 13)
  - Of Victims Arrive (Box 82, Folder 14)
  - Secret Spot (Box 82, Folder 15)
  - Jojo Kenn (Box 82, Folder 16)
  - Novak (Box 82, Folder 17)
  - Mecca Normal (Box 82, Folder 18)
  - The Cannanes (Box 82, Folder 19)
  - Suu's (Box 82, Folder 20)
  - The Motor Totemist Guild (Box 82, Folder 21)
  - Shorty Long (Box 82, Folder 22)
  - IXNA (Box 82, Folder 23)
  - Richard Berry and the Silks (Box 82, Folder 24)
  - James Himself (Box 82, Folder 25)
  - XFR Experiments in the Future of ReadingMar-Sep 2000 (Box 83, Folder 2)
  - Pattern and Perception: Interfaces of Art, Physics, and Code5/20/2003 (Box 83, Folder 3)
  - New Music America: A festival organized by the Walker Art Center6/1/1980 (Box 83, Folder 5)
- Series 12: World Economics
  - Notebook (Box 34)
  - Annual Meeting 2001 Report (Box 34)
  - Report on the Annual Meeting 2000 (Box 34)
  - Annual Meeting 2000 Participants List (Box 34)
  - Photos (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Forum Daily News (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Newsweek Special Edition "Issues 2000"1999 (Box 35)
  - The View from Davos "Responsible Globality" Report on the 1999 Annual Meeting of the World Economic Forum1999 (Box 35)
  - Forum Fellows at the Annual Meeting 20002000 (Box 35)
  - Annual Meeting 2000 Programme2000 (Box 35)
  - Annual Meeting 2001 Programme2001 (Box 35)
  - Annual Meeting 1999 Programme1999 (Box 35)
  - Trip Report 2001 World Economic Forum2001 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Welcome Card, Kongress Hotel Davos2001 (Box 35, Folder 2)
- Series 13: Xerox Parc
  - Auditory Interfaces: The Use of Non-Speech Audio at the Interface (Box 36)
  - Art By Xerox Report 19931993 (Box 36)
  - The Fine Art History of Notre Dame Football by Steven Ernest Csorba1995 (Box 36)
  - Copy Art Show1993 (Box 36)
  - The Document Company (Box 36)
  - Tab Project Review Pre-reading1993 September (Box 36)
  - A Stylus-based User Interface for Text: Entry and Editing1991 May (Box 36)
  - Computer Science Laboratory Technical Report Digest: 1973-19901991 November (Box 36)
  - PARC identity (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - US Patent, Want et al (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Cyborg Talk1995 October (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - PARC - 25 Photos (Box 36, Folder 4)